SCRAPED_CLINIC_SERVICES = {
    "Advanced Foot Care Bargara": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Resources",
    "Advanced Foot Care Bundaberg": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Resources",
    "Advanced Foot Care Hervey Bay": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Albany Creek": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Seniors Footcare, Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Calamvale": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Seniors Footcare, Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Camp Hill": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Seniors Footcare, Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Forest Lake": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Hawthorne": "Sports podiatry, Digital Gait analysis, Custom Orthotics, Paediatric assessments, Footwear assessments",
    "Allsports Podiatry Indooroopilly": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Seniors Footcare, Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Kangaroo Point": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Noosa": "General podiatry care, Ingrown toenail treatment, Custom foot orthotics, Video gait analysis, Diabetic footcare, Seniors footcare, Paediatric assessments",
    "Allsports Podiatry Red Hill": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry The Gap": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Toowong": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Allsports Podiatry Wavell Heights": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Anytime Physio & Podiatry Newstead": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare",
    "Back In Motion Podiatry Bacchus Marsh": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, SWIFT Microwave Wart Therapy",
    "Back In Motion Podiatry Bayswater": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Seniors Footcare, Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts",
    "Back In Motion Podiatry Bundall": "Surgical Podiatry, Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Custom Foot Orthotics, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Seniors Footcare, Shockwave Therapy, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "Back In Motion Podiatry Burleigh Waters": "Surgical Podiatry, Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Custom Foot Orthotics, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Seniors Footcare, Shockwave Therapy, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "Back In Motion Podiatry Como": "Clinical Podiatry, Shockwave Therapy",
    "Back In Motion Podiatry Melton": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, SWIFT Microwave Wart Therapy",
    "Border Podiatry Wodonga": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources",
    "Ispahan Podiatry": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Aldinga": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Resources",
    "My FootDr Ballarat": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Resources, Footwear",
    "My FootDr Bathurst": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "My FootDr Beerwah": "Surgical Podiatry, Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Seniors Footcare, Resources, Video Gait Analysis, Custom Footwear",
    "My FootDr Blacktown": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "My FootDr Blackwood": "Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Boronia": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Brisbane CBD": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Footwear",
    "My FootDr Brookside": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Brookwater": "Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Burwood": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Cairns": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Resources",
    "My FootDr Camp Hill": "Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Fungal Nail Diafactory Testing, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Custom Cricket Shoes, Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Cobra9 Cycling Orthotics, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, SWIFT Microwave Wart Therapy, Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Casula": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Resources",
    "My FootDr Cessnock": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS)",
    "My FootDr Charlestown": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear",
    "My FootDr Christies Beach": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Cleveland": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment",
    "My FootDr Cranbourne": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS)",
    "My FootDr Currambine": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Custom Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Devonport": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Footwear",
    "My FootDr Dubbo": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Fortitude Valley": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Footwear",
    "My FootDr Gladstone": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Gumdale": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Hope Island": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Hove": "Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Indooroopilly": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Resources",
    "My FootDr Ipswich": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "My FootDr Jindalee": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "My FootDr Mackay": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Mittagong": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Modbury": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources, Richie Brace",
    "My FootDr Moorebank": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Resources",
    "My FootDr Mt Gravatt": "Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Narellan": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Resources",
    "My FootDr North Lakes": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "My FootDr Orange": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Pakenham": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Palmerston": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Red Hill": "Custom Foot Orthotics, Ankle-Foot Orthoses, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS)",
    "My FootDr Redcliffe": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Rockhampton": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Shailer Park": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Stafford": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Stirling": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Thuringowa": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Toowoomba": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Townsville": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "My FootDr Tweed Heads": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses",
    "My FootDr Unley": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Resources",
    "My FootDr Varsity Lakes (formerly Robina)": "Surgical Podiatry, Clinical Podiatry, Custom Foot Orthotics, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Seniors Footcare, Shockwave Therapy",
    "My FootDr Wantirna": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Supramalleolar Orthotics (SMOs), Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cam Walker - (Moon Boot), Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Ankle-Foot Orthoses, Richie Brace",
    "My FootDr Warragul": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, SWIFT Microwave Wart Therapy, Resources",
    "My FootDr Warwick": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), Custom Footwear, CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Footwear, Resources",
    "My FootDr Wembley Downs": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources, Footwear",
    "My FootDr Woodville": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS)",
    "My FootDr Yeppoon": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "NQ Foot & Ankle Centre Cowboys Centre of Excellence": "Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Shockwave Therapy",
    "NQ Foot & Ankle Centre Kirwan": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Shockwave Therapy, Resources",
    "Physiologic Podiatry Robina": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Resources",
    "Semaphore (formerly Queenstown)": "Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Diabetes and Footcare, Shockwave Therapy",
    "The Foot and Ankle Clinic Moe": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "The Foot and Ankle Clinic Podiatry Chadstone": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "The Foot and Ankle Clinic Podiatry East Bentleigh": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "The Foot and Ankle Clinic Sale": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, Resources",
    "The Foot and Ankle Clinic Traralgon": "BracenfixÖ - Ingrown Toenail Treatment, Clinical Podiatry, Health Funds, Custom Foot Orthotics, Video Gait Analysis, Fungal Nail Infection Laser Treatment, Diabetes and Footcare, Custom Footwear, National Disability Insurance Scheme (NDIS), CAM Walker (Moon Boot), Cosmetic Nail Restoration, Shockwave Therapy, Footwear, Paraffin Wax Bath Treatment, Cryotherapy For Plantar Warts, SWIFT Microwave Wart Therapy, Resources",
}

Wrote snippet to d:\Work\Mindrift\scripts\scraped_services_mapping_snippet.txt
